<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<topics>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/401-AH</num>
		<title>Euro Inflation</title>
		<desc>Find documents about rises in prices after the introduction of the Euro.</desc>
		<narr>Any document is relevant that provides information on the rise of prices in any country that introduced the common European currency.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/402-AH</num>
		<title>Renewable Energy Sources</title>
		<desc>Find documents reporting on the exploitation of renewable resources for power/energy production.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will report on the use of power obtained from renewable resources, such as biomass, water, solar, geothermal or wind power. Information on energy-saving vehicles is not relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/403-AH</num>
		<title>Acting as a Cop</title>
		<desc>Find documents that give information about actors playing police roles in films or television.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will mention the title of the film, play or series, as well as the name of the actor or the actress who played the part of the policeman or women.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/404-AH</num>
		<title>NATO Summit Security</title>
		<desc>Find reports that describe the on-site security measures at any NATO summit.</desc>
		<narr>We seek information concerning security precautions taken on the sites of NATO summits anywhere in the world. Information concerning incidents, demonstrations, and protest actions against the summit are not relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/405-AH</num>
		<title>Childhood Asthma</title>
		<desc>What conditions can trigger asthma in children?</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will cite some or all of the main factors  believed to be responsible for the onset of asthma in children.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/406-AH</num>
		<title>Animated Cartoons</title>
		<desc>Find documents about animated cartoons that have been considered for a prize or award.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents name at least one animated cartoon that was either presented at a film festival in the hope of winning a prize or was under consideration for an award independently of any festival.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/407-AH</num>
		<title>Australian Prime Minister</title>
		<desc>Who was the Australian Prime Minister in 2002?</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must give the name of the Australian Prime Minister in charge in 2002.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/408-AH</num>
		<title>Human Cloning</title>
		<desc>We seek any information on human cloning including claims of the production of the first human clone.</desc>
		<narr>We are interested in information on improvements in the cloning of human embryos. Organizations engaged in cloning, methods of cloning, the potential for  medicine, and laws regulating problems related to cloning are all of an interest to us.  Documents discussing ethical problems are not of interest.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/409-AH</num>
		<title>Bali Car Bombing</title>
		<desc>Retrieve documents reporting the nationality of the victims of a terrorist car bomb in Bali, Indonesia, in 2002.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must mention the nationality or country of origin of the Indonesian car bomb victims.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/410-AH</num>
		<title>North Korea Nuclear Weapons Violation</title>
		<desc>Find documents providing evidence that North Korea is violating the 1994 nuclear agreement to freeze its nuclear weapons program.</desc>
		<narr>Evidence considered relevant includes facts like the moving of fuel into a reactor, or preventing UN control of plants. North Korean admissions that  they have restarted work on the production of atomic weapons is also relevant. However, unproven claims by other governments or by journalists are not relevant, and neither are threats by the North Koreans of a possible future production.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/411-AH</num>
		<title>Best Picture Oscar</title>
		<desc>What movie was awarded the Oscar for best film in March 2002?</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must provide not only the name of the movie but also of the director.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/412-AH</num>
		<title>Books on Politicians</title>
		<desc>Find documents that discuss books on politicians.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents discuss or review books written about politicians such as biographies, pamphlets, collections of anecdotes, etc.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/413-AH</num>
		<title>Reducing Diabetes Risk</title>
		<desc>Find documents mentioning factors that reduce the risk of the onset of diabetes.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will discuss at least one factor that is believed to prevent or reduce the risk of diabetes of any kind.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/414-AH</num>
		<title>Beer Festivals</title>
		<desc>Find documents describing  beer festivals such as the Oktoberfest or similar.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must mention the place where the beer festival is or was organized.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/415-AH</num>
		<title>Drug Abuse</title>
		<desc>Find documents that discuss any efforts to solve or control the phenomenon of drug abuse and addiction.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will report attempts to solve drug abuse problems in individual countries  and regions. Documents of interest include information on drug crisis centers, attempts to legalize certain types of drugs, prevention of drug-related diseases. Information on crimes related to the production or consumption of narcotics is not of interest.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/416-AH</num>
		<title>Moscow Theatre Hostage Crisis</title>
		<desc>How did the Russian authorities end the Moscow theater crisis in which Chechen Rebels held about 700 hostages?</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will report on the final action  taken by Russian authorities to put an end to the hostage-taking by a group of Chechen rebels and on the outcomes of their actions. Documents reporting on the hostage-taking without any information on how it ended are not relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/417-AH</num>
		<title>Airplane Hijacking</title>
		<desc>We seek documents on both successful and unsuccessful  hijacking of planes and information on the airlines or countries involved.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents will provide details on actual plane hijacking attempts and should include information on either the airline or the countries involved. Documents discussing the aftermath of the 9/11 terrorist attacks are not relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/418-AH</num>
		<title>Bülent Ecevit's Statements</title>
		<desc>Find documents that report the Turkish Prime Minister Bülent Ecevit's public statements.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents contain any public statement made by the Turkish Prime Minister Bülent Ecevit. Documents discussing Ecevit's politics and/or serious illness but not quoting Ecevit are not relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/419-AH</num>
		<title>Nuclear Waste Repositories</title>
		<desc>Retrieve documents that discuss some advantages or disadvantages of  using designated controlled and centralised sites for the storage of nuclear waste.</desc>
		<narr>Documents reporting issues related to storage of nuclear waste in specific locations are not relevant. Relevant articles must discuss the usefulness or danger  of having centralised nuclear waste repositories rather than leaving radioactive waste scattered over many different sites.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/420-AH</num>
		<title>Obesity and Ill-health</title>
		<desc>What health problems are possibly caused at least partly by overweight or obesity?</desc>
		<narr>Any document that discusses ways in which excessive weight or obesity can deteriorate the state of health and names at least one pertinent illness or group of illnesses counts as relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/421-AH</num>
		<title>Kostelic Olympic Medals</title>
		<desc>What medals did the Kostelic siblings win at the Winter Olympics in 2002?</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must give details on the medals won by either Janica or Ivica Kostelic at the Salt Lake Olympics. The document must state clearly the name of the event and the colour of the medal: gold, silver or bronze.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/422-AH</num>
		<title>Industrial and Business Closures</title>
		<desc>Find information on the actual or imminent closing down of factories or businesses of any type.</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must report on the reasons for actual or threatened closure.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/423-AH</num>
		<title>Alternatives to Flu Shots</title>
		<desc>Find documents that report on alternative measures to vaccinations against influenza .</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must mention the name or provide details of the alternative measure proposed.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/424-AH</num>
		<title>Internet Banking Increase</title>
		<desc>Find documents that provide numerical information on the growing popularity of internet banking services.</desc>
		<narr>Any document that includes numerical data on the countries, companies or individual clients taking advantage of online or net banking services counts as relevant.</narr>
	</top>
	<top lang="en">
		<num>10.2452/425-AH</num>
		<title>Endangered Species</title>
		<desc>Find documents discussing the killing, poaching or illegal fishing of protected or endangered species of any kind (mammal, bird or fish).</desc>
		<narr>Relevant documents must mention the endangered species threatened by illegal actions. Documents that regard animals that are not in danger of extinction are not relevant.</narr>
	</top>
</topics>